Mohamed Roshdy Ahmed

Address: Cairo – Mohandseen Mobile: 01010536968

E-mail: mhmdrshdy29@gmail.com

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/mohamed-roshdy-b63105119

Career Objective:

Individual with well-honed skills in computer science and technical expertise in the support of specialized programming projects using web based and client server tools. Interested in the job of a Software Developer. Coming with strong ability to design, develop, and maintain software applications

Education:

9 Month Diploma of System Development,
Professional Web Development & BI track,
Information Technology Institute Oct 2019 to July 2020.

- Faculty of Science, Minia University, Physics & computer science Department,

Section 2011-2015. General Grade: Good.

Graduation project Grade: Excellent.

Technical Background:

-Programming Language C Programming, C++ and C#.

- Desktop Applications Windows Forms, WPF.

-Web Technology Asp.net, MVC 5, .Net Core 3.0, Entity Framework 6, LINQ

ADO.Net, Angular 9, Ajax, WCF, Web API and Signal R

-Client Side HTML5, Css3, Bootstrap, JavaScript, Type Script

and JQuery.

- Database SQL Server 2017, SQL Admin and BI

-Others UML, XML, Agile methodology, Windows Azure.

Tools:

-SQl Server 2017, Visual Studio 2019 and Visual Studio Code.

Experiences:

- Internship Web Developer at Taqnia from (3/12/2018 to 30/6/2019)

- Digital Support Specialist at WE (TE-Data previously) (5/9/2017 – 2/12/2018)

- Technical Support at WE (TE-Data previously) (4/11/2016- 5/9/2017).

Projects:

- Project Name: Library Web App.,

Description: Site for Library management,

Worked On: ITI,

Tools: SQl Server 2017, Visual Studio 2019, MVC, Repository Design Pattern,

JQuery and Bootstrap.

- Project Name: Freelancing Zone,

Description: Site for manage Freelancing Zone of ITI,

Worked On: ITI.

Tools: SQl Server 2017, Visual Studio 2019, MVC, Ajax, JQuery and Bootstrap.

- Project Name: E-commerce,

Description: Site for manage sales for products, Worked On: ITI.

Tools: Angular 9, SQl Server 2017, Visual Studio 2019, Web API,

Ajax, HTML5, JQuery and Bootstrap.

- Project Name: Examination System,

Description: Desktop Application,

Worked On: ITI,

Tools: SQl Server 2017, Visual Studio2019, WCF.

Languages:

Arabic: Mother language.

English: Very Good.

Courses:

- Microsoft Web Development Diploma at CLS Learning (2/6/2018 to 13/10/2018)

- English course at (Not Courses level 7)

References and Documentations Will Be Available Upon Request.